<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Felipe Kinoshita <kinofhek@gmail.com>
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2022 Nate Graham <nate@kde.org>
-->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.plasma-welcome</id>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Welcome Center</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مركز الترحيب</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Centru d'acoyida</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">Salamlama mərkəzi</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Азнаямляльны цэнтр</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Център за приветствие и първоначални настройки</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Centre de benvinguda</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Centre de benvinguda</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Uvítací centrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Begrüßungsassistent</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Welcome Center</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Centro de bienvenida</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Ongietorri Gunea</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Tervetulokeskus</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Centre de bienvenue</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Centro de benvida</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">מרכז קבלת הפנים</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Üdvözlőközpont</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Centro de Benvenite</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Welcome Center</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Kynningarmiðstöð</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Centro di benvenuto</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">მისალმების ცენტრი</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">환영 센터</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Supažindinimas su sistema</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Uzņemšanas centrs</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Welkomstcentrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Velkomst­senter</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਜੀ ਆਇਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਕੇਂਦਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Powitalnia</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Centro de Boas-Vindas</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Centro de boas vindas</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Centru de întâmpinare</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Помощник первого запуска</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">स्वागत केन्द्रम्</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Uvítacie centrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Središče za dobrodošlico</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Välkomstcenter</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">வரவேற்பு மையம்</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Вітальний центр</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Centerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">欢迎中心</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">歡迎中心</name>
  <summary>Friendly onboarding wizard for Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">معالج ترحيب لسطح مكتب بلازما</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="az">Plasmanın ilk açılışında mehriban qarşılama bələdçisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Зручны памагаты для Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Помощник за начални настройки за Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Assistent d'incorporació amistosa per al Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent d'incorporació amistosa per a Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Průvodce pro příjemný začátek s prostředím Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Der freundliche Begrüßungsassistent für Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Friendly on-boarding wizard for Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Amika familiariĝosorĉisto por Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Asistente de incorporación amigable para Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Plasmaren harrera-morroi lagunkoia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Ystävällinen tervetulo-opastus Plasmaan</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Assistant intégré sympathique pour Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Asistente de incorporación fácil de usar para Plasma.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">אשף ידידותי לקבלת פנים לפלזמה</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Barátságos bevezető varázsló a Plasmához</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Amicabile assistente de integration per Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Wizard orientasi yang ramah untuk Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Vinalegt kynningarforrit fyrir Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Procedura guidata amichevole per il primo approccio a Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">Plasma-სთან დამეგობრების ოსტატი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">친근한 Plasma 환영 마법사</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Plasma draugiškas darbo pradžios vediklis</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Draudzīgs uzņemšanas vednis „Plasma“ darbvirsmai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Vriendelijke assistent voor Plasma aan boord</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Hjelpsam rettleiar for nye Plasma-brukarar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਪਲਾਜ਼ਮਾ ਲਈ ਸਰਲ ਸਵਾਗਤੀ ਸਹਾਇਕ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przyjazne przyjęcie na pokładzie Plazmy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um assistente de acolhimento amigável para o Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um assistente de integração amigável para o Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Asistent prietenos pentru inițiere în Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Дружелюбный мастер приветствия при первом запуске Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">प्लाज्मा कृते मैत्रीपूर्णः समागमनः विजार्डः</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Priateľský úvodný sprievodca pre Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Čarovnik dobrodošlice na krovu Plasme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Vänlig introduktionsguide för Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ta">பிளாஸ்மாவை பயனர்களுக்கு அறிமுகப்படுத்தும் உதவிநிரல்</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Plasma İlk Kullanım Sihirbazı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Дружній майстер початкового налаштовування для Плазми</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFriendly onboarding wizard for Plasmaxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">Plasma 新手向导程序</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">Plasma 用的友善介紹精靈</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Welcome Center is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customize the system, and more!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مركز الترحيب هو مقدمة مثالية لبلازما كِيدِي! يمكن أن يساعدك على تعلم كيفية الاتصال بالإنترنت وتثبيت التطبيقات وتخصيص النظام والمزيد!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">¡El centru d'acoyida ye la presentación perfeuta de KDE Plasma! Pue ayudate a deprender cómo conectate a internet, instalar aplicaciones, personalizar el sistema y muncho más.</p>
    <p xml:lang="az">Salamlama mərkəzi KDE Plasmaya ən yaxşı girişdir! Bu, internetə qoşulmağa, tətbiqləri quraşdırmağa, sistemdə dəyişiklik etməyə ilkin yardım göstərəcək!</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Азнаямляльны цэнтр - гэта ідэальны сродак уводзін ў KDE Plasma! Ён дапаможа вам навучыцца падлучацца да інтэрнэту, усталёўваць праграмы, наладжваць сістэму і многае іншае!</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Центърът за приветствие е идеалното въведение в KDE Plasma! Той може да ви помогне да научите как да се свързвате с интернет, да инсталирате приложения, да персонализирате системата и още много други неща!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El centre de benvinguda és la introducció perfecta al Plasma de KDE! Pot ajudar-vos a aprendre com connectar-vos a Internet, instal·lar aplicacions, personalitzar el sistema, i més!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El centre de benvinguda és la introducció perfecta a Plasma de KDE! Pot ajudar-vos a aprendre com connectar-vos a Internet, instal·lar aplicacions, personalitzar el sistema, i més!</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Der Begrüßungsassistent ist die perfekte Einführung in KDE Plasma. Er kann Ihnen helfen, sich mit dem Internet zu verbinden, Anwendungen zu installieren, das System an Ihre Bedürfnisse anzupassen und vieles mehr.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customise the system, and more!</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Bonvencentro estas la perfekta enkonduko al KDE Plasma! Ĝi povas helpi vin lerni kiel konekti al la interreto, instali aplikojn, proprigi la sistemon kaj pli!</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El centro de bienvenida es la introducción perfecta a KDE Plasma. Le puede ayudar a aprender a conectarse a Internet, instalar aplicaciones, personalizar el sistema, y mucho más.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ongietorri Gunea KDE Plasmarako harrera perfektua da! Internetera nola konektatu, aplikazioak nola instalatu, sistema zure gustura egokitzen eta gehiago ikasten lagunduko dizu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tervetulokeskus on täydellinen johdatus KDE Plasmaan! Se auttaa yhdistämään internetiin, asentamaan sovelluksia, mukauttamaan järjestelmää ja paljon muuta!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le Centre de bienvenue est l'introduction parfaite à KDE Plasma ! Il peut vous aider à apprendre comment vous connecter à Internet, installer des applications, personnaliser le système, et plus encore !</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O centro de benvida é a introdución perfecta a KDE Plasma! Pode axudarlle a aprender a conectarse a Internet, instalar aplicacións, personalizar o sistema, e moito máis!</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מרכז קבלת הפנים הוא צורת ההיכרות הטובה ביותר עם פלזמה מבית KDE! הוא יכול לסייע לך ללמוד איך להתחבר לאינטרנט, להתקין יישומים, לשנות את תצורת המערכת ועוד!</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Üdvözlőközpont a tökéletes bevezetés a KDE Plasmába! Segítségével megtanulhatja, hogyan csatlakozzon az internethez, telepítsen alkalmazásokat, szabja testre a rendszert, és még sok minden mást!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Welcome Center (Centro de benvenite) es le perfecte introduction a KDE Plasma! Illo pote adjutar te a apprender como connecter a internet, installar apps, personalisar le systema e plus!</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Welcome Center adalah pengenalan sempurna untuk KDE Plasma! Ini bisa membantu Anda mempelajari cara terkoneksi ke internet, menginstal aplikasi, menyesuaikan sistem, dan banyak lagi!</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Kynningarmiðstöðin er tilvalin kynning á KDE Plasma! Hún getur sýnt þér hvernig hægt er að tengjast netinu, setja upp forrit, sérsníða tölvuna og fleira!</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Centro di benvenuto è l'introduzione perfetta a Plasma di KDE! Può aiutarti a imparare come connetterti a Internet, installare applicazioni, personalizzare il sistema e altro ancora!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">მისალმების ცენტრი KDE Plasma-ის საუკეთესო წარდგენაა! მას შეუძლია, დაგეხმაროთ, ისწავლოთ, როგორ მიუერთდეთ ინტერნეტს, დააყენოთ აპები, მოირგოთ სისტემა და ბევრი სხვა!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">환영 센터는 KDE Plasma를 소개합니다! 인터넷에 연결하기, 앱 설치하기, 시스템 사용자 정의 등을 소개합니다!</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Supažindinimas su sistema pateikia puikių patarimų apie KDE Plasma! Jis gali jus išmokyti, kaip prisijungti prie interneto, įdiegti programas, tinkinti sistemą ir kt.!</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Uzņemšanas centrs ir lielisks ievads darbam ar KDE „Plasma“! Tas var palīdzēt iemācīties, kā pieslēgties pie interneta, instalēt programmas, pielāgot sistēmu un daudz ko citu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Welkomcentrum is de perfecte introductie in KDE Plasma! Het kan u helpen te leren hoe u een verbinding maakt met het internet, toepassingen installeert, het systeem aanpast en meer!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Velkomstsenteret gjev ei fin innføring i KDE Plasma for nye brukarar. Det kan hjelpa deg å kopla til Internett, installera program, tilpassa brukarflata etter eigne behov og mykje anna.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਜੀ ਆਇਆਂ ਨੂੰ KDE ਪਲਾਜ਼ਮਾ ਲਈ ਸਭ ਤੋਂ ਵਧੀਆ ਜਾਣ-ਪਛਾਣ ਹੈ! ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਇੰਟਰਨੈੱਟ ਨਾਲ ਕਨੈਕਟ ਕਰਨ, ਐਪਾਂ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨੂੰ ਆਪਣੇ ਮੁਤਾਬਕ ਢਾਲਣ ਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਕਈ ਕੁਝ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਸਿੱਖਣ ਲਈ ਮਦਦ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Powitalnia jest doskonałym wprowadzeniem do Plazmy KDE! Pomoże połączyć z internetem, wgrywać aplikacje, dostosować system i więcej!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Centro de Boas-Vindas é a introdução perfeita ao Plasma do KDE! Podê-lo-á ajudar a aprender a ligar-se à Internet, a instalar aplicações, personalizar o sistema, entre outras coisas!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O centro de boas vindas é uma ótima introdução ao KDE Plasma! Pode te ajudar a aprender como se conectar à internet, instalar aplicativos, personalizar o sistema e mais!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Centrul de întâmpinare e inițierea perfectă în KDE Plasma! Acesta vă ajută să învățați cum să vă conectați la internet, să instalați aplicații, să personalizați sistemul, și altele!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Помощник первого запуска — прекрасное введение в KDE Plasma! Он рассказывает, как настроить подключение к сети, установить приложения, настроить систему под себя и не только.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">स्वागतकेन्द्रं KDE Plasma इत्यस्य सम्यक् परिचयः अस्ति! अन्तर्जालसङ्गणकेन सह सम्बद्धतां, अनुप्रयोगं संस्थापयितुं, प्रणालीं अनुकूलितुं, इत्यादीनि च ज्ञातुं साहाय्यं कर्तुं शक्नोति!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Uvítacie centrum je dokonalým úvodom do prostredia KDE Plasma! Pomôže vám naučiť sa, ako sa pripojiť na internet, inštalovať aplikácie, prispôsobiť systém a mnoho ďalšieho!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Središče dobrodošlice je popoln uvod v KDE Plasma! Lahko vam pomaga, da se naučite, kako vzpostaviti povezavo z internetom, namestiti aplikacije, prilagoditi sistem in še več!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Välkomstcenter är den perfekta introduktionen till KDE Plasma! Det kan hjälpa dig att lära dig hur du ansluter till Internet, installerar program, anpassar systemet med mera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ta">வரவேற்பு மையம், உங்களுக்கு கே.டீ.யீ. பிளாஸ்மாவை அறிமுகப்படுத்தும். இணையத்தில் இணைவது, செயலிகளை நிறுவுவது, கணினியை மாற்றியமைப்பது போன்ற அடிப்படையானவற்றைக் நீங்கள் கற்றுகொள்ள உதவும்.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi, KDE Plasma için en iyi tanıtımı alabileceğiniz biricik yazılımdır. Size; internete bağlanmayı, uygulamalar kurmayı, sistemi özelleştirmeyi ve çok daha fazlasını gösterir!</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Вітальний центр є чудовим вступом до Плазми KDE! Він може допомогти вам дізнатися про те, як встановити з'єднання з інтернетом, встановити програми, налаштувати систему тощо!</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Center is the perfect introduction to KDE Plasma! It can help you learn how to connect to the internet, install apps, customize the system, and more!xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">欢迎中心是 KDE Plasma 的初次上手向导程序。它可以帮助您学习如何连接到互联网、安装应用、自定义系统以及使用其他功能。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">歡迎中心是對 KDE Plasma 的完美初次簡介！它可以幫您學習如何連線到網際網路、安裝應用程式、自訂系統等等！</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-1.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome Center first page: introducing KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">الصفحة الأولى من مركز الترحيب: تقدم كِيدِي بلازما</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ast">Primer páxina del centru d'acoyida: Presentación de KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="az">Salamlama mərkəzinin ilk səhifəsi: KDE Plasmaya giriş</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Першая старонка азнаямляльнага цэнтра: уводзіны ў KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Първа страница на центъра за приветствие: представяне на KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Primera pàgina del centre de benvinguda: presentació del Plasma de KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Primera pàgina del centre de benvinguda: presentació de Plasma de KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Erste Seite des Begrüßungsassistenten: Einführung in KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre first page: introducing KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Welcome Center unua paĝo: enkondukante KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Primera página del centro de bienvenida: presentación de KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ongietorri Guneko lehen orria: KDE Plasmaren sarrerakoa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tervetulokeskuksen ensimmäinen sivu: johdanto KDE Plasmaan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La première page du « Centre de bienvenue » : présentation de KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Primeira páxina do centro de benvida: introdución a KDE Plasma.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד ראשון במרכז קבלת הפנים: היכרות עם פלזמה מבית KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Az Üdvözlőközpont első oldala: a KDE Plasma bemutatása</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Prime pagina de Welcome Center (Centro de Benvenite): introducer KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman pertama Welcome Center: memperkenalkan KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Kynningarmiðstöð, fyrsta síða: við kynnum KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Prima pagina del Centro di benvenuto: introduzione a KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მისალმების ცენტრის პირველი გვერდი: წარმოგიდგენთ KDE Plasma-ს</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">환영 센터 첫 페이지: KDE Plasma 소개</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Supažindinimas su sistema, pirmas puslapis: KDE Plasma pristatymas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Uzņemšanas centra pirmā lapa: iepazīstināšana ar KDE „Plasma“</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Eerste pagina Welkomcentrum: introductie tot KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Velkomstsenter, første side: innføring i KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਜੀ ਆਇਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਕੇਂਦਰ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਸਫ਼਼ਾ: ਕੇਡੀਈ ਪਲਾਜ਼ਮਾ ਨਾਲ ਜਾਣ-ਪਛਾਣ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Pierwsza strona powitalni: przedstawienie Plazmy KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Primeira página do Centro de Boas-Vindas: introdução ao Plasma do KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Primeira página do centro de boas vindas: introduzindo o KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Centru de întâmpinare, prima pagină: introducerea KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Первая страница приложения: представление KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">स्वागतकेन्द्रस्य प्रथमपृष्ठम्: KDE Plasma परिचयः</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Prvá stránka Uvítacieho centra: predstavenie KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Prva stran središča za dobrodošlico: predstavitev KDE Plasme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välkomstcentrets första sida: Introduktion av KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ta">வரவேற்பு மையத்தின் முதற்பக்கம்: பிளாஸ்மாவிற்கான அறிமுகம்</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi ilk sayfası: KDE Plasma’ya hoş geldiniz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перша сторінка «Вітального центру»: вступ до Плазми KDE</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Center first page: introducing KDE Plasmaxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">欢迎中心第一页：介绍 KDE Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">歡迎中心的第一頁：KDE Plasma 簡介</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-2.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome Center second page: how to install apps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">الصفحة الثانية من مركز الترحيب: كيف تثبت التطبيقات</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ast">Segunda páxina del centru d'acoyida: Cómo instalar aplicaciones</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="az">Slamalama mərkəzinin ikinci səhifəsi: tətbiqləri necə quraşdırmalı</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Другая старонка азнаямляльнага цэнтра: як усталёўваць праграмы</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Втора страница на центъра за приветствие: как се инсталират приложения</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Segona pàgina del centre de benvinguda: com instal·lar aplicacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Segona pàgina del centre de benvinguda: com instal·lar aplicacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Zweite Seite des Begrüßungsassistenten: Installation von Anwendungen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre second page: how to install apps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Welcome Center dua paĝo: kiel instali aplikojn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Segunda página del centro de bienvenida: cómo instalar aplicaciones</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ongietorri Guneko bigarren orria: aplikazioak nola instalatu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tervetulokeskuksen toinen sivu: miten asentaa sovelluksia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La seconde page du « Centre de bienvenue » : comment installer des applications</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Segunda páxina do centro de benvida: como instalar aplicacións.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד שני במרכז קבלת הפנים: איך להתקין יישומים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Az Üdvözlőközpont második oldala: hogyan telepíthetők alkalmazások</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Secunde pagina de Welcome Center (centro de Benvenite): como installar apps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman kedua Welcome Center: cara memasang aplikasi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Kynningarmiðstöð, önnur síða: hvernig á að setja upp forrit</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Seconda pagina del Centro di benvenuto: come installare le applicazioni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მისალმების ცენტრის მეორე გვერდი: როგორ დავაყენოთ აპები</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">환영 센터 두 번째 페이지: 앱 설치</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Supažindinimas su sistema, antras puslapis: kaip įdiegti programas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Uzņemšanas centra otrā lapa: programmu instalēšanas pamācība</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tweede padina Welkomcentrum: hoe toepassingen installeren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Velkomstsenter, andre side: korleis installera program</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਜੀ ਆਇਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਕੇਂਦਰ ਦੂਜਾ ਸਫ਼ਾ: ਐਪਾਂ ਕਿਵੇਂ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰੀਏ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Druga strona powitalni: jak wgrywać programy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Segunda página do Centro de Boas-Vidas: como instalar aplicações</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Segunda página do centro de boas vindas: como instalar aplicativos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Centru de întâmpinare, pagina doi: cum se instalează aplicații</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Вторая страница помощника: как устанавливать приложения</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">स्वागतकेन्द्रं द्वितीयं पृष्ठम्: अनुप्रयोगाः कथं संस्थाप्यन्ते</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Druhá stránka Uvítacieho centra: ako inštalovať aplikácie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Druga stran središča za dobrodošlico: kako namestiti aplikacije</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välkomstcentrets andra sida: Hur man installerar program</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ta">வரவேற்பு மையத்தின் இரண்டாம் பக்கம்: செயலிகளை நிறுவும் முறை</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi ikinci sayfası: Uygulama kurma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Друга сторінка «Вітального центру»: як встановлювати програми</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Center second page: how to install appsxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">欢迎中心第二页：如何安装应用</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">歡迎中心的第二頁：如何安裝應用程式</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/plasma-welcome/plasma-welcome-page-6.png</image>
      <caption>Welcome Center sixth page: how to get involved</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">الصفحة السادسة من مركز الترحيب: كيف يمكنك المشاركة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ast">Sesta páxina del centru d'acoyida: Cómo andechar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="az">Salamlama mərkəzinin altıncı səhifəsi: proqram tərtibatına necə töhvə vermək olar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Шостая старонка азнаямляльнага цэнтра: як далучыцца</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Шеста страница на центъра за приветствие: как да помогнем</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Sisena pàgina del centre de benvinguda: com col·laborar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sisena pàgina del centre de benvinguda: com col·laborar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Sechste Seite des Begrüßungsassistenten: Mitmachen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Welcome Centre sixth page: how to get involved</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Welcome Center sesa paĝo: kiel involviĝi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Sexta página del centro de bienvenida: cómo implicarse</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ongietorri Guneko seigarren orria: nola engaiatu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tervetulokeskuksen kuudes sivu: miten osallistua toimintaan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La sixième page du « Centre de bienvenue » : comment contribuer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Sexta páxina do centro de benvida: como colaborar.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד שישי במרכז קבלת הפנים: איך לקחת חלק</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Az Üdvözlőközpont hatodik oldala: hogyan lehet bekapcsolódni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Centro de Benvenite sexte pagina: como esser implicate</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman keenam Welcome Center: cara terlibat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Kynningarmiðstöð, sjötta síða: hvernig hægt er að taka þátt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Sesta pagina del Centro di benvenuto: come partecipare</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მისალმების ცენტრის მეექვსე გვერდი: როგორ დაგეხმაროთ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">환영 센터 여섯 번째 페이지: 참여하기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Supažindinimas su sistema, šeštas puslapis: kaip įsitraukti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Uzņemšanas centra sestā lapa: kā iesaistīties</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Zesde pagina Welkomcentrum: hoe mee te doen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Velkomstsenter, sjette side: korleis bidra sjølv</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਜੀ ਆਇਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਕੇਂਦਰ ਛੇਵਾਂ ਸਫ਼ਾ: ਹਿੱਸਾ ਕਿਵੇਂ ਲਈਏ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Szósta strona powitalni: jak współtworzyć</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Sexta página do Centro de Boas-Vidas: como se envolver no projecto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Primeira página do centro de boas vindas: como se envolver</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Centru de întâmpinare, pagina șase: cum să vă implicați</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Шестая страница приложения: как присоединиться к разработке</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">स्वागतकेन्द्रं षष्ठं पृष्ठम् : कथं सम्मिलितं भवितव्यम्</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Šiesta stránka Uvítacieho centra: ako sa zapojiť</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Šesta stran središča za dobrodošlico: kako biti vpleten</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välkomstcentrets sjätte sida: Hur man engagerar sig</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ta">வரவேற்பு மையத்தின் ஆறாவது பக்கம்: பங்களிக்கும் முறை</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Karşılama Merkezi altıncı sayfası: Nasıl katılabilirim</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Шоста сторінка «Вітального центру»: як взяти участь у проєкті</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxWelcome Center sixth page: how to get involvedxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">欢迎中心第六页：如何参与贡献</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">歡迎中心的第六頁：如何參與</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/plasma/plasma-welcome</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=Welcome%20Center</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/plasma/plasma-welcome</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=welcome-center&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.plasma-welcome.desktop</launchable>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <compulsory_for_desktop>KDE</compulsory_for_desktop>
  <releases>
    <release version="6.1.3" date="2024-07-16"/>
    <release version="6.1.2" date="2024-07-02"/>
    <release version="6.1.1" date="2024-06-25"/>
    <release version="6.1.0" date="2024-06-18"/>
  </releases>
</component>
