<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<protocol name="treeland_foreign_toplevel_manager_v1">
    <copyright>
        Copyright © 2023 Uniontech

        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a
        copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"),
        to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation
        the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
        and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
        Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

        The above copyright notice and this permission notice (including the next
        paragraph) shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the
        Software.

        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL
        THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
        FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER
        DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
    </copyright>
    <interface name="ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_manager_v1" version="1">
        <description summary="foreign toplevel manager">
            This interface allows a client to get toplevel some info.

            Warning! The protocol described in this file is currently in the testing
            phase. Backward compatible changes may be added together with the
            corresponding interface version bump. Backward incompatible changes can
            only be done by creating a new major version of the extension.
        </description>
        <event name="toplevel">
            <description summary="a toplevel has been created">
                This event is emitted whenever a new toplevel window is created. It
                is emitted for all toplevels, regardless of the app that has created
                them.

                All initial details of the toplevel(title, app_id, states, etc.) will
                be sent immediately after this event via the corresponding events in
                ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1.
            </description>
            <arg name="toplevel" type="new_id" interface="ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1" />
        </event>
        <request name="stop">
            <description summary="Stop sending events">
                Indicates the client no longer wishes to receive events for new toplevels.
                However the compositor may emit further toplevel_created events, until
                the finished event is emitted.

                The client must not send any more requests after this one.
            </description>
        </request>
        <event name="finished" type="destructor">
            <description summary="the compositor has finished with the toplevel manager">
                This event indicates that the compositor is done sending events to the
                ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_manager_v1. The server will destroy the object
                immediately after sending this request, so it will become invalid and
                the client should free any resources associated with it.
            </description>
        </event>
        <request name="get_dock_preview_context">
            <arg name="relative_surface" type="object" interface="wl_surface" />
            <arg name="id" type="new_id" interface="treeland_dock_preview_context_v1" />
        </request>
    </interface>
    <interface name="ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1" version="1">
        <description summary="An opened toplevel">
            A ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1 object represents an opened toplevel window. Each
            app may have multiple opened toplevels.

            Warning! The protocol described in this file is currently in the testing
            phase. Backward compatible changes may be added together with the
            corresponding interface version bump. Backward incompatible changes can
            only be done by creating a new major version of the extension.
        </description>
        <event name="pid">
            <description summary="Process id of application owning the window has changed">
                This event will be sent when the compositor has set the process id this window
                belongs to. This should be set once before the initial_state is sent.
            </description>
            <arg name="pid" type="uint" />
        </event>
        <event name="title">
            <description summary="title change">
                This event is emitted whenever the title of the toplevel changes.
            </description>
            <arg name="title" type="string" />
        </event>

        <event name="app_id">
            <description summary="app-id change">
                This event is emitted whenever the app-id of the toplevel changes.
            </description>
            <arg name="app_id" type="string" />
        </event>
        <event name="identifier">
            <description summary="a stable identifier for a toplevel">
                The identifier of each top level and its handle must be unique.
                Two different top layers cannot have the same identifier.
                This identifier is only valid as long as the top level is mapped.
                Identifiers must not be reused if the top level is not mapped.
                The compositor must not reuse identifiers to ensure there are no races when identifiers are shared between processes.
            </description>
            <arg name="identifier" type="uint" />
        </event>

        <event name="output_enter">
            <description summary="toplevel entered an output">
                This event is emitted whenever the toplevel becomes visible on
                the given output. A toplevel may be visible on multiple outputs.
            </description>
            <arg name="output" type="object" interface="wl_output" />
        </event>

        <event name="output_leave">
            <description summary="toplevel left an output">
                This event is emitted whenever the toplevel stops being visible on
                the given output. It is guaranteed that an entered-output event
                with the same output has been emitted before this event.
            </description>
            <arg name="output" type="object" interface="wl_output" />
        </event>

        <request name="set_maximized">
            <description summary="requests that the toplevel be maximized">
                Requests that the toplevel be maximized. If the maximized state actually
                changes, this will be indicated by the state event.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="unset_maximized">
            <description summary="requests that the toplevel be unmaximized">
                Requests that the toplevel be unmaximized. If the maximized state actually
                changes, this will be indicated by the state event.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="set_minimized">
            <description summary="requests that the toplevel be minimized">
                Requests that the toplevel be minimized. If the minimized state actually
                changes, this will be indicated by the state event.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="unset_minimized">
            <description summary="requests that the toplevel be unminimized">
                Requests that the toplevel be unminimized. If the minimized state actually
                changes, this will be indicated by the state event.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="activate">
            <description summary="activate the toplevel">
                Request that this toplevel be activated on the given seat.
                There is no guarantee the toplevel will be actually activated.
            </description>
            <arg name="seat" type="object" interface="wl_seat" />
        </request>

        <enum name="state">
            <description summary="types of states on the toplevel">
                The different states that a toplevel can have. These have the same meaning
                as the states with the same names defined in xdg-toplevel
            </description>

            <entry name="maximized" value="0" summary="the toplevel is maximized" />
            <entry name="minimized" value="1" summary="the toplevel is minimized" />
            <entry name="activated" value="2" summary="the toplevel is active" />
            <entry name="fullscreen" value="3" summary="the toplevel is fullscreen" />
        </enum>

        <event name="state">
            <description summary="the toplevel state changed">
                This event is emitted immediately after the ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1
                is created and each time the toplevel state changes, either because of a
                compositor action or because of a request in this protocol.
            </description>

            <arg name="state" type="array" />
        </event>

        <event name="done">
            <description summary="all information about the toplevel has been sent">
                This event is sent after all changes in the toplevel state have been
                sent.

                This allows changes to the ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1 properties
                to be seen as atomic, even if they happen via multiple events.
            </description>
        </event>

        <request name="close">
            <description summary="request that the toplevel be closed">
                Send a request to the toplevel to close itself. The compositor would
                typically use a shell-specific method to carry out this request, for
                example by sending the xdg_toplevel.close event. However, this gives
                no guarantees the toplevel will actually be destroyed. If and when
                this happens, the ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1.closed event will
                be emitted.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="set_rectangle">
            <description summary="the rectangle which represents the toplevel">
                The rectangle of the surface specified in this request corresponds to
                the place where the app using this protocol represents the given toplevel.
                It can be used by the compositor as a hint for some operations, e.g
                minimizing. The client is however not required to set this, in which
                case the compositor is free to decide some default value.

                If the client specifies more than one rectangle, only the last one is
                considered.

                The dimensions are given in surface-local coordinates.
                Setting width=height=0 removes the already-set rectangle.
            </description>

            <arg name="surface" type="object" interface="wl_surface" />
            <arg name="x" type="int" />
            <arg name="y" type="int" />
            <arg name="width" type="int" />
            <arg name="height" type="int" />
        </request>

        <enum name="error">
            <entry name="invalid_rectangle" value="0"
                summary="the provided rectangle is invalid" />
        </enum>

        <event name="closed">
            <description summary="this toplevel has been destroyed">
                This event means the toplevel has been destroyed. It is guaranteed there
                won't be any more events for this ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1. The
                toplevel itself becomes inert so any requests will be ignored except the
                destroy request.
            </description>
        </event>

        <request name="destroy" type="destructor">
            <description summary="destroy the ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1 object">
                Destroys the ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1 object.

                This request should be called either when the client does not want to
                use the toplevel anymore or after the closed event to finalize the
                destruction of the object.
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="set_fullscreen">
            <description summary="request that the toplevel be fullscreened">
                Requests that the toplevel be fullscreened on the given output. If the
                fullscreen state and/or the outputs the toplevel is visible on actually
                change, this will be indicated by the state and output_enter/leave
                events.

                The output parameter is only a hint to the compositor. Also, if output
                is NULL, the compositor should decide which output the toplevel will be
                fullscreened on, if at all.
            </description>
            <arg name="output" type="object" interface="wl_output" allow-null="true" />
        </request>

        <request name="unset_fullscreen">
            <description summary="request that the toplevel be unfullscreened">
                Requests that the toplevel be unfullscreened. If the fullscreen state
                actually changes, this will be indicated by the state event.
            </description>
        </request>

        <event name="parent">
            <description summary="parent change">
                This event is emitted whenever the parent of the toplevel changes.

                No event is emitted when the parent handle is destroyed by the client.
            </description>
            <arg name="parent" type="object" interface="ztreeland_foreign_toplevel_handle_v1"
                allow-null="true" />
        </event>
    </interface>
    <interface name="treeland_dock_preview_context_v1" version="1">
        <description summary="handle dock preview">
            This interface allows dock set windows preview.

            Warning! The protocol described in this file is currently in the testing
            phase. Backward compatible changes may be added together with the
            corresponding interface version bump. Backward incompatible changes can
            only be done by creating a new major version of the extension.
        </description>

        <enum name="direction">
            <description summary="types of direction on the dock preview">
            </description>

            <entry name="top" value="0" summary="top" />
            <entry name="right" value="1" summary="right" />
            <entry name="bottom" value="2" summary="bottom" />
            <entry name="left" value="3" summary="left" />
        </enum>

        <event name="enter">
            <description summary="enter preview box">
                This event is sent after mouse enter preview box.
            </description>
        </event>
        <event name="leave">
            <description summary="leave preview box">
                This event is sent after mouse leave preview box.
            </description>
        </event>

        <request name="show">
            <description summary="set preview surfaces">
                X and Y are relative to the relative_surface.
                surfaces wl_array is identifiers.
            </description>

            <arg name="surfaces" type="array" />
            <arg name="x" type="int" />
            <arg name="y" type="int" />
            <arg name="direction" type="uint" />
        </request>

        <request name="close">
            <description summary="close preview box">
                close preview box
            </description>
        </request>

        <request name="destroy" type="destructor">
            <description summary="destroy the context object">
                Destroy the context object.
            </description>
        </request>
    </interface>
</protocol>
