<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.sweeper.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <name>Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الكناس</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Escombraire</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Agranador</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">स्वीपर</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ie">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Spazzino</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Išvalymo įrankis</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਸਵੀਪਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Czyściciel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Zametač</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Чистач</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Čistač</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Чистач</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Čistač</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Süpürücü</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Sweeper</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSweeperxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Sweeper 系统清理工具</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Sweeper</name>
  <summary>System cleaning utility</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">أداة تنظيف النظام</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за почистване на системата</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Utilitat de neteja del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Utilitat de neteja del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro úklid systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Redskab til at rense systemet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Dienstprogramm zum Bereinigen des Systems</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εργαλείο καθαρισμού του συστήματος</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">System cleaning utility</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Utilidad de limpieza del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Süsteemi puhastamise tööriist</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Sistema garbitzeko baliagarritasuna</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Järjestelmän siivoustyökalu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Utilitaire de nettoyage du système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Utilidade de limpeza do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">तंत्र सफाई उपयोगिता</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Rendszertisztító segédprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Utilitate per nettar le systema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Utilitas pembersihan sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ie">Utensile de nettation del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Kerfishreinsunarartól</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Utilità per la pulizia del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სისტემის გასუფთავების პროგრამა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템 청소 도구</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Sistemos išvalymo paslaugų programa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddel voor opschonen van het systeem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Verktøy for dataopprydding</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸਫ਼ਾਈ ਸਹੂਲਤ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do czyszczenia systemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Utilitário de limpeza do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Utilitário de limpeza do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Приложение для очистки системы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na čistenie systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Orodje za čiščenje sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Алатка за чишћење система</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Alatka za čišćenje sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Алатка за чишћење система</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Alatka za čišćenje sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Systemrensningsverktyg</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sistem temizleme izlencesi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для чищення системи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSystem cleaning utilityxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">系统清理工具</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">系統清理工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Sweeper helps to clean unwanted traces the user leaves on the system. It
      can remove cookies and clean out caches, for example.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الكناس يساعد في تنظيف الأثآر غير المرغوبة التي يتركها المستخدم في النظام. على سبيل المثال يمكنه إزالة الكعكات (ملفات التعريف) وينظف الخبيئة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Sweeper е програма, която помага да се почистят нежеланите следи, които потребителят оставя в системата. Тя може да например да премахва бисквитки и да почиства кеша.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'escombraire ajuda a netejar el rastre no desitjat que va deixant l'usuari al sistema. Elimina les galetes i neteja les memòries cau, per exemple.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'agranador ajuda a netejar el rastre no desitjat que va deixant l'usuari al sistema. Elimina les galetes i neteja les memòries cau, per exemple.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Sweeper pomáhá smazat nechtěné stopy zanechané uživatelem v systému. Například může mazat cookies a mezipaměť.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Sweeper hjælper med at rydde op i uønskede spor som brugeren har efterladt på systemet. Den fjerner f.eks. cookies og rydder op i cacher.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Sweeper hilft dem Benutzer ungewollte Spuren im System zu verwischen und kann zum Beispiel Cookies und Zwischenspeicher bereinigen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Sweeper βοηθάει στον καθαρισμό ανεπιθύμητων ιχνών που ο χρήστης αφήνει στο σύστημα. Μπορεί να αφαιρέσει cookies και να καθαρίσει προσωρινές μνήμες, για παράδειγμα.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Sweeper helps to clean unwanted traces the user leaves on the system. It can remove cookies and clean out caches, for example.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Sweeper ayuda a borrar el rastro no deseado que deja el usuario en el sistema. Puede eliminar cookies y borrar cachés, por ejemplo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Sweeper aitab kõrvaldada soovimatud jäljed, mida kasutaja süsteemi jätab. Näiteks võib see eemaldada küpsised ja puhastada puhvrid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Sweeperrek erabiltzaileak sisteman uzten dituen nahigabeko arrastoak garbitzen ditu. Kukiak kendu ditzake eta cacheak garbitu, esaterako.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Sweeper auttaa poistamaan käyttäjän järjestelmään jättämät turhat jäljet. Se osaa esimerkiksi poistaa evästeet ja tyhjentää välimuistit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Sweeper aide à effacer les traces indésirables laissées par l'utilisateur sur le système. Il peut supprimer les cookies et vider les caches, par exemple.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Sweeper axuda a limpar os restos sen usar que o usuario deixa no sistema. Pode eliminar cookies e cachés, por exemplo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">स्वीपर उपयोक्ता द्वारा तंत्र पर छोड़े गए अवांछित निशानों को साफ करने में मदद करता है। उदाहरण के लिए, यह कुकीज़ को हटा सकता है और कैश को साफ कर सकता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Sweeper segít a nem kívánt nyomok törlésében a rendszerből. Többek között eltávolítja a sütiket és kiüríti a gyorsítótárakat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Sweeper adjuta nettar tracias non volite que le usator lassa in le systema. Il pote remover cookies e nettar caches pro exemplo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Sweeper membantu membersihkan jejak yang tidak diinginkan yang ditinggalkan pengguna pada sistem. Itu dapat menghapus cookie dan membersihkan cache, misalnya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">Sweeper efacia índesirat tracies quel li usator lassa in li sistema. Por exemple, it posse remover cookies e caches.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Sweeper hjálpar til við að hreinsa óþarfar slóðir sem notandinn skilur eftir á kerfinu. Það getur endurheimt diskpláss með því t.d. að fjarlægja vefkökur og ónotaðar bráðabirgðaskrár.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Lo spazzino aiuta a cancellare le tracce indesiderate che l'utente lascia nel sistema, ad esempio può rimuovere i cookie e ripulire la cache.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Sweeper დაგეხმარებათ მომხმარებლის მიერ სისტემაში დატოვებული არასასურველი კვალი მოასუფთავოთ. მას, მაგალითად, ქუქიების წაშლა და ქეშების გასუფთავება შეუძლია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Sweeper는 시스템에 남아 있는 사용자의 과거 기록을 청소합니다. 쿠키와 캐시 등 데이터를 지울 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Išvalymo įrankis padeda išvalyti nepageidaujamus pėdsakus, kuriuos naudotojas palieka sistemoje. Šis įrankis, pavyzdžiui, gali pašalinti slapukus ir išvalyti podėlius.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Sweeper helpt bij het uitwissen van ongewenste sporen die de gebruiker op het systeem achterlaat. Het kan bijvoorbeeld cookies verwijderen en caches opschonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Sweeper hjelper deg å fjerna uønskte spor på datamaskina. Du kan blant anna bruka det til å fjerna infokapslar og mellom-/snøgglager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Czyściciel pomaga zatrzeć niechciane ślady, które użytkownik zostawia na systemie. Może na przykład usunąć ciasteczka, a także wyczyścić pamięci podręczne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Sweeper ajuda a limpar os vestígios indesejados que o utilizador deixa no sistema. Poderá remover os 'cookies' e limpar as 'caches', por exemplo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Sweeper ajuda a limpar os vestígios indesejados que o usuário deixa no sistema. Ele pode remover os cookies e apagar os 'caches', por exemplo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение предназначено для удаления следов работы пользователя в операционной системе, таких как файлы cookie и кешированные файлы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Zametač vám pomôže vyčistiť neželané stopy, ktoré používateľ zanecháva v systéme. Môže napríklad odstrániť cookies a vyčistiť vyrovnávacie pamäte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Sweeper pomaga pri čiščenju neželenih sledi, ki jih uporabnik pušča na sistemu. Med drugim lahko odstrani piškotke in predpomnilnike.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Чистач помаже у отклањању нежељених трагова које корисник остави на систему. На пример, може да уклања колачиће и чисти кешеве.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Čistač pomaže u otklanjanju neželjenih tragova koje korisnik ostavi na sistemu. Na primer, može da uklanja kolačiće i čisti keševe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Чистач помаже у отклањању нежељених трагова које корисник остави на систему. На пример, може да уклања колачиће и чисти кешеве.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Čistač pomaže u otklanjanju neželjenih tragova koje korisnik ostavi na sistemu. Na primer, može da uklanja kolačiće i čisti keševe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Sweeper hjälper till att rensa oönskade spår som användaren lämnar i systemet. Det kan exempelvis ta bort kakor och tömma cachar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Süpürücü, kullanıcının sistemde bıraktığı istenmeyen izleri temizlemenize yardımcı olur. Örneğin, çerezleri kaldırır ve önbellekleri boşaltır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Sweeper допомагає позбутися небажаних слідів роботи користувача у системі. Зокрема, програма може вилучати записи кук та спорожняти кеш.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSweeper helps to clean unwanted traces the user leaves on the system. It can remove cookies and clean out caches, for example.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Sweeper 可以清理系统中的用户使用记录，例如 Cookies 缓存等。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://utils.kde.org/projects/sweeper/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=sweeper</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=sweeper</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=sweeper&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/sweeper/sweeper.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>sweeper</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05"/>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08"/>
  </releases>
</component>
